drivers.com 2002-12-04

# Drivers.com - Privacy Policy

### Privacy and Exchange of Information at Drivers.com

Thank you for taking a moment to read our policy on visitor privacy and exchange of information. Drivers.com believes trust and confidence are important concerns when dealing with visitors by e-mail and on the Internet. 

To address those concerns, [PDE Publications Inc.](http://www.drivers.com/corporate.shtml) has formulated this statement of policy and practice regarding privacy and exchange of information on the Drivers.com web site: 

## SUMMARY

We collect information from our users at several different points on our web site, including through the use of automated "cookies." Users provide personal information to us only if they wish to do so. Financial information is never shared with companies other than the financial institutions required to finalize the transaction. If you wish to change or modify information previously provided to Drivers.com, use our [Contact Us page](http://www.drivers.com/contact.shtml), or send an e-mail request to [admin@Drivers.com](mailto:admin@Drivers.com). 

## DETAILS

### Information Collection and Use

PDE Publications Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. PDE collects information from our users at several different points on our web site. 

### Product Orders

We request information from the user on our product order form. Here a user must provide contact information (such as name and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

### Cookies

A "cookie" is an anonymous identifier (a unique number) stored as a tiny piece of data on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. This information does not include any personally identifiable data (such as name, address, or e-mail address) that is considered sensitive or controversial or would compromise a consumer's privacy. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. We never attempt to match cookie information to personal information (such as a name) that users voluntarily provide in certain sections of our site such as on order or feedback forms. 

### Log Files

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number used to represent a computer on the Internet. When a computer accesses the Internet through an ISP, it typically receives a temporary IP address. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

### Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. At certain times, we partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

### Third Party Advertising

We use DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information ( **not** including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

**Third Party Cookies—** In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. (See the section on cookies, above.) 

### Newsletters

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletters, we ask for contact information such as name and e-mail address. 

### Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as postal code, or age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

### Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information (such as a postal address) changes, or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update, or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done by using our [Contact Us page](http://www.drivers.com/contact.shtml), or by sending e-mail to [admin@Drivers.com](mailto:admin@Drivers.com). 

### Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to "opt-out" of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletters or other services may opt-out by using our [Contact Us page](http://www.drivers.com/contact.shtml), or by sending e-mail to [admin@Drivers.com](mailto:admin@Drivers.com). 

### Contacting Drivers.com

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your business dealings with this site, please email [admin@Drivers.com](mailto:admin@Drivers.com) or use the form on the [Contact Us page](http://www.drivers.com/contact.shtml). Thank you for your interest in our policy on visitor privacy, and in Drivers.com in general. We hope your questions have been answered satisfactorily. 

* * *

For all inquiries please contact the publisher: 

> **PDE Publications Inc.**   
>  310–5334 Yonge Street   
>  Toronto, Ontario, Canada   M2N 6M2   
>  Telephone: (416) 767-4885   
>  Fax: (416) 767-7425   
>  E-Mail: [pde@Drivers.com](mailto:pde@Drivers.com)   
>  Web: [http://www.Drivers.com](http://www.drivers.com/)

* Please use our [Contact Us page](http://www.drivers.com/contact.shtml) for **detailed inquiries.**
* If you would like to be part of the growth of our site, and can write interesting and informative articles about driving and drivers, please [contact us](http://www.drivers.com/contact.shtml) about becoming a **contributing writer.**
* **To advertise with Drivers.com** , refer to our [rate card](http://www.drivers.com/ratecard.shtml) for details.
